Ms Janet DORNAN, MIET, BEng

Warwickshire

Email: j.dornan@physics.org Mobile: 07890 284497 Website: https://janet-dev.github.io

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/janetdornan/ GitHub: @janet-dev

JavaScript	HTML	css
Ruby	Industrial UI	Bootstrap
Python	Git	Skeleton

Software developer and ex-industrial UI engineer with over ten years' experience in the control industry.

Highly motivated with excellent research skills, which enabled the building of a product-based website.

Team player, but also comfortable with working alone.

Skilled at multitasking, managing time effectively and prioritising tasks in line with the business.

Excellent at communication, both verbally and written, as well as confident with social media platforms.

Able to team manage and facilitate department meetings.

Possess advanced customer service skills in dealing with the public or business clients.

Well versed in mentoring both customers and clients on new departmental standards.

Career Professional Development

Code First Girls Introduction to Python Programming

25 Feb - 15 Apr 2021 (remote with CFG)

freeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design

Mar 2021 Basic HTML & CSS Completed

Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures
Mar 2021 Basic JavaScript Completed

Code First Girls CFG: MOOCs Introduction to React.is

Feb 2021

Codecademy Learn Ruby

Feb 2021

Code First Girls Introduction to Web Development

06 Oct - 24 Nov 2020 (remote with everis)

InsideSherpa Commonwealth Bank Virtual Internship Participant - Careers in Tech

Jul – Sep 2020 Design (UX/UI), Software Engineering, Cyber Security,

Data Science and Analytics, AI / Robotics

codebar Student member

Aug 2020 - present

WildCodeSchool Prep. Courses: Data Analyst, Web Developer

Jul - Aug 2020

Office Skills

- Microsoft Office (Microsoft Excel, Access, Word, PowerPoint), Open Office, Libre Office
- Graphics / HMI (Human Machine Interface) / UI design packages used within the control system industry
- Windows, OS X and Linux operating systems (Ubuntu/Mint)
- WordPress for self hosted website building
- Social media for marketing Instagram, Facebook, Pinterest, TikTok, YouTube
- Canva for marketing and branding
- Manual data analysis within a small bakery

Employment History

09/2016 – Present	Non-coding roles	Various
01/2016 - 04/2016	Field Services Engineer (*HMI)	Schneider Electric (Invensys UK)
01/2012 – 10/2014	Field Services Engineer (*HMI)	Invensys Systems Nigeria
02/2010 - 01/2012	Non-coding roles	Various
01/2009 – 01/2010	Graphics Engineer (*HMI)	Honeywell Process Systems
08/2002 – 12/2008	Applications Engineer (*HMI)	GroupCytek

^{*}HMI – Human Machine Interface (UI / GUI / Industrial Control Graphics)

Education:

University of Oxford PGCert in Software and Systems Security

Apr 2015 – Oct 2018

RGIT (RGU), Aberdeen BEng(Hons) in Electronic and Electrical Engineering

Strathearn School, Belfast NIGCE: Maths – B, English – B

Languages: Basic: Russian, German, French

Professional Memberships: Member of the Institution of Engineering and Technology

Member of the Institute of Physics

Interests: Designing and marketing own handmade artisan jewellery

Keen allotment owner, growing vegetables and tortoise food